Contact

valery1.alexis@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/valery-alexisfuturemha (LinkedIn)

Valery Alexis RN, MHA

Front Line Leader RN Care Coach at Conviva Care Solutions
Miami/Fort Lauderdale Area

Summary

I am an experienced Healthcare Administrative Professional with a demonstrated history of working in Care Facilitation Leadership, Care Coordination, Nursing Management, and Discharge Planning. I enjoy helping my patients strive to live and be at their best.

Experience

Conviva Care Centers

2 years 5 months

Front Line Leader RN Care Coach

January 2020 - Present (7 months)

Boca Raton, Florida

Care Facilitation for Palm Beach County

RN Care Coach

March 2018 - January 2020 (1 year 11 months)

Boca Raton, Florida

Humana

Care Coordinator

September 2017 - March 2018 (7 months)

Broward Health

8 years 5 months

Critical Care/ Coronary Care Registered Nurse

May 2015 - September 2017 (2 years 5 months)

Fort Lauderdale, FL

Endoscopy/ GI Registered Nurse

April 2014 - May 2015 (1 year 2 months)

Coral Springs, FL

Cardiac Care Registered Nurse

May 2009 - April 2014 (5 years)

Fort Lauderdale, FL

Education

Florida Atlantic University

Master of Health Administration, Business Administration and Management, General \cdot (2019 - 2020)

Florida Agricultural and Mechanical University
Bachelor of Science - BS, Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2006 - 2008)

Florida Atlantic University
Associate of Arts - AA · (2004 - 2006)